{"Biology":{"Bio 101":{"Appendix Review":[{"group":"","stem":"Which direction do a person's palms face in the anatomical position?","choices":["forward (frontal)","backwards (posteriorly)","",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"A coronal (frontal) section of the head divides the head into:","choices":["left and right sides","top and bottom","front and back",""],"correct":["2"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"A saggital section divides the body into:","choices":["left and right sides","top and bottom","front and back",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"What region is the heart located in?","choices":["Thorax (Mediastinum)","Abdomen","Pelvis",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"What region are the lungs located in?","choices":["Thorax","Abdomen","Pelvis",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"What cavity are the lungs located in?","choices":["Thoraxic (pleural)","Abdominal","Pelvic",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"The intestines are located in what region/cavity?","choices":["Abdomen/abdominal","Pelvis/pelvic","Thorax/thoracic",""],"correct":["0"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"The urinary bladder is located in what region?","choices":["Abdomen","Pelvis","Thorax",""],"correct":["1"],"nota":false},{"group":"","stem":"Your armpits are in what body region?","choices":["Umbilical","Pubic","Crural","Axilary"],"correct":["3"]},{"group":"","stem":"What region is your voice box in?","choices":["Cervical","Thoracic","Lumbar","Sacral"],"correct":["0"]},{"group":"","stem":"Which region is the brain in?","choices":["Cephalic&nbsp;","Vertebral","Femoral","Cervical"],"correct":["0"]},{"group":"","stem":"The heart is ____________ to the lungs?","choices":["Superior","Posterior","Lateral","Medial"],"correct":["3"]},{"group":"","stem":"The wrist is ____________ to the elbow?","choices":["Anterior","Inferior","Distal","Proximal"],"correct":["2"]},{"group":"","stem":"The elbow is ____________ to the wrist?","choices":["Anterior","Inferior","Distal","Proximal"],"correct":["3"]},{"group":"","stem":"The kneecap is on the __________ side of the body?","choices":["Anterior","Posterior","Superior","Inferior"],"correct":["0"]},{"group":"","stem":"The naval is __________ to the rib cage?","choices":["Superior","Inferior","Anterior","Posterior"],"correct":["1"]},{"group":"","stem":"The spine is __________ to the stomach?","choices":["Superior","Inferior","Anterior","Posterior"],"correct":["3"]},{"group":"","stem":"The muscles are __________ to the skin?","choices":["Superficial","Deep","Anterior","Superior"],"correct":["1"]},{"group":"","stem":"The ears are __________ to the nose?","choices":["Medial","Lateral","Distal","Posterior"],"correct":["1"]},{"group":"","stem":"The skin is __________ to the bones.","choices":["Superficial","Deep","Anterior","Superior"],"correct":["0"]},{"group":"","stem":"What seperates the abdominal and thoracic cavities?","choices":["Diaphragm","Pelvis","Lungs","Stomach"],"correct":["0"]},{"group":"","stem":"The eyes are located in the __________ cavity.","choices":["Orbital","Oral","Axillary","Thoracic"],"correct":["0"]}]}}}